10/2/2018 Your Resume



**■** BOJANMADZARACKA@GMAIL.COM [] 091/755-4977

#### Date: 02 October 2018

I am a young programmer in the making. The amount of my experience is within my own personal projects. Some of them are simple learning projects that will never be deployed, while others are more advanced projects in the domain of Web development and design.

I am well versed in procedural and object oriented programming, MVC architecture, and test driven development. Although my main focus for the time being is server-side development, necessity has driven me to learn javascript, CSS and HTML5 as well as some more advanced technologies like Vue 2 and SASS, which I do plan on mastering as well.

Though my time in active programming might seem short I assure you that I have more than compensated for that in concentrating most of my free time and focus into learning and mastering what I found to be the one unchanging thing throughout my life, my love and interest in programming.

Which brings me to the reason for my wish to work with you and your team. The scope of the project at hand and its never ending need for improvement makes it the perfect environment for me. The chance to learn from such a big project and improve myself is too great to pass by, so I am sure that if you take a chance and give me one to prove myself, you will not be disappointed and will find out that I can be an ever-improving asset to both you and your project.

I look forward to hearing from You or one of Your team.

# BOJAN MADŽARAC

## **■** BOJANMADZARACKA@GMAIL.COM ☐ 091/755-4977

In HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/BOJAN-MADŽARAC-8B7929B3/

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-taught programmer that has spent most of his life dabbling in code. At an age of 26 I have decided to dig deeper in software development and have since spent almost all of my free time writing code. From smaller procedural scripts to larger MVC based web pages. How the scope of my ambitions grew so did my skills and methods, from a beginner writing code in c++ through my first solo hobby-project of making a landing page in php, html5 and css to my latest project where I use Laravel, Vue.js and SASS to create a fully responsive Web app. Afterwards i have mostly moved to the Smyfony 4 framework, however i still use both depending on the circumstances.

I vigorously seek out knowledge, new technologies and techniques to improve myself. What I lack in experience I will more than make up with my ability and will to learn and improve. I wholeheartedly believe that those that meet and talk to me will see my potential and will not be disappointed in my work and effort.

# EXPERIENCE

## WAITER

NARCA // VARAŽDIN // 2010-2011 Worked as a waiter through collage years

## WAITER

LAVRA // VARAŽDIN // 2012-2013 Worked as a waiter

### SALES AGENT

VIP D.O.O // ZAGREB // 2013-2014
Worked as a sales agent in a telecommunication company

#### BARMAN

MOJA DIRIDIKA - PAPAS BAR // KARLOVAC // 2014-2015 Worked as a barman/barkeep

## WAREHOUSE WORKER

KAUFLAND D.O.O // JASTREBARSKO // 2015-2016 Warehouse worker - packaging and shipment

#### **KEY-USER IN TRAINING**

BOXMARK LEATHER D.O.O. // VARAŽDIN // 11.01.2016. - 11.01.2017

Managed daily SAP interactions and inventory lists, as well as handled potential problems in production related to SAP and PPA systems

## INCOMING MATERIAL QUALITY INSPECTOR

BOXMARK LEATHER D.O.O. // VARAŽDIN // 11.01.2017. - NOW

Managed incoming material certificates and suppliers as well as handled any potential problems they might cause.

10/2/2018 Your Resume

# **EDUCATION**

# **COMPUTER TECHNICIAN**

TEHNIČKA ŠKOLA KARLOVAC // KARLOVAC, CROATIA // 2009

# SKILLS —

PHP // OOP // MVC PROGRAMMING ARCHITECTURE // WEB DEVELOPMENT //
LARAVEL // JAVASCRIPT // VUE.JS // TEST DRIVEN DEVELOPMENT // PHPUNIT //
SQL // HTML5 // CSS // XML // C++ // AJAX // MICROSOFT OFFICE // GITHUB //
XAMPP // WAMPP // DATA MANAGEMENT // WEB DESIGN // SYMFONY 4 //
DOCTRINE // GIT